<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>Deployment - Category - Welcome to Thai&#39;s Home</title>
        <link>https://hpthai7.github.io/categories/deployment/</link>
        <description>Deployment - Category - Welcome to Thai&#39;s Home</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><managingEditor>th3ho@yahoo.com (Thai Ho)</managingEditor>
            <webMaster>th3ho@yahoo.com (Thai Ho)</webMaster><copyright>This work is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial 4.0 International License.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Thu, 23 Apr 2020 00:00:00 &#43;0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://hpthai7.github.io/categories/deployment/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item>
    <title>Git Flows for Management of Software Projects</title>
    <link>https://hpthai7.github.io/git-flows-overview/</link>
    <pubDate>Thu, 23 Apr 2020 00:00:00 &#43;0000</pubDate>
    <author>Author</author>
    <guid>https://hpthai7.github.io/git-flows-overview/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[This article covers the different git flows tailored for software projects in professional environment. Each flow is adapted to the context of project scale, the number of developers and the expected delivery cycles. Here we feature Git Flow, Github Flow, Gitlab Flow
Git Flow Github Flow Gitlab Flow Refence  Gitlab tutorial Stackoverflow Semantic release   ]]></description>
</item><item>
    <title>Kubernetes Cheat Sheet</title>
    <link>https://hpthai7.github.io/kubernetes-cheat-sheet/</link>
    <pubDate>Mon, 13 Apr 2020 00:00:00 &#43;0000</pubDate>
    <author>Author</author>
    <guid>https://hpthai7.github.io/kubernetes-cheat-sheet/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[What is Kubernetes Kubernetes is a sophisticated tool for the orchestration of containers in mass deployment. It provides an effective ways to define the software components, resources and deploy them in a controllable and effective manner. The strongest points of Kubernetes is:
  The abstraction of infrastructure layer to deployment layer. This allows developers and administrators concentrate on the development stage and less worry about the management of the underlying hardware settings.]]></description>
</item><item>
    <title>Virtualization vs Containerization</title>
    <link>https://hpthai7.github.io/virtualization-vs-containerization/</link>
    <pubDate>Mon, 13 Apr 2020 00:00:00 &#43;0000</pubDate>
    <author>Author</author>
    <guid>https://hpthai7.github.io/virtualization-vs-containerization/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Semantic versioning The versioning of docker images, as per Docker Hub, does not respect the rules of semantic versioning. A single image can share different tags as demonstrated in the photo. The tags feature a Major release, a Major.minor release, and a Major.minor.patch release.]]></description>
</item></channel>
</rss>
