<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>development - Tag - LoveIt</title>
        <link>https://hpthai7.github.io/tags/development/</link>
        <description>development - Tag - LoveIt</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><managingEditor>th3ho@yahoo.com (Thai Ho)</managingEditor>
            <webMaster>th3ho@yahoo.com (Thai Ho)</webMaster><copyright>This work is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial 4.0 International License.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Wed, 08 Nov 2017 00:00:00 &#43;0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://hpthai7.github.io/tags/development/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item>
    <title>Clean Code - A Handbook of Agile Software Craftsmanship</title>
    <link>https://hpthai7.github.io/clean-code-a-handbook-of-agile-software-craftmanship/</link>
    <pubDate>Wed, 08 Nov 2017 00:00:00 &#43;0000</pubDate>
    <author>Author</author>
    <guid>https://hpthai7.github.io/clean-code-a-handbook-of-agile-software-craftmanship/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[During an internship, I inherited a big project in insurance, featuring the processing and visualization of natural-phenomenon-related risk data and decision making of insurance contracts. The big words of contracts, forewriting,
Quotes:
&ldquo;If I don’t do what my manager says, I’ll be fired.&rdquo; Probably not. Most managers want the truth, even when they don’t act like it. Most managers want good code, even when they are obsessing about the schedule. They may defend the schedule and requirements with passion; but that’s their job.]]></description>
</item><item>
    <title>(Hu)go Template Primer</title>
    <link>https://hpthai7.github.io/hugo-template-primer/</link>
    <pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2014 00:00:00 &#43;0000</pubDate>
    <author>Author</author>
    <guid>https://hpthai7.github.io/hugo-template-primer/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Hugo uses the excellent Go html/template library for its template engine. It is an extremely lightweight engine that provides a very small amount of logic. In our experience that it is just the right amount of logic to be able to create a good static website. If you have used other template systems from different languages or frameworks you will find a lot of similarities in Go templates.
This document is a brief primer on using Go templates.]]></description>
</item><item>
    <title>Getting Started with Hugo</title>
    <link>https://hpthai7.github.io/getting-started-with-hugo/</link>
    <pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2014 00:00:00 &#43;0000</pubDate>
    <author>Author</author>
    <guid>https://hpthai7.github.io/getting-started-with-hugo/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Step 1. Install Hugo Go to Hugo releases and download the appropriate version for your OS and architecture.
Save it somewhere specific as we will be using it in the next step.
More complete instructions are available at Install Hugo
In Windows The handy way favors chocolatey. For the theme KeepIt, it&rsquo;s recommended to install the extended version of hugo with SCSS/SASS support. It allows better rendering of the website thanks to the generation of CSS in resources directory from SCSS/SASS styles.]]></description>
</item></channel>
</rss>
